Alright, I run my code
and, uh, this one creates a table one as we have
defined the mapping sheet.
Table one is getting created here.
We group by, by these dimensions, these fields,
and we want to calculate these fields, in fact.
And the aggregation functions are defined here.
So all of this is coded right here.
In fact, you are grouping by the dimensions, the fields,
and you are aggregating as per the mapping sheet.
And then, uh, that's table one. We also have table two.
Likewise, what you see here is table two.
We are grouping by, uh, the different fields we see here.
And then, uh, getting the
aggregated values using these functions.
And that is what you see here in this particular code.
And if you scroll down, we also have
the table three getting created, um,
based on the mapping sheet again.
Okay? And finally, when we are all done,
we will be loading the data back into Data Lake.
That is what is done here, in fact.
So for Jan 2024,
the data is loaded back into data lake, okay?
The information, uh, as to where it is loaded is right here.
And these different S3 parts, okay?
Within aggregated and within daily borrow daily zone,
and daily service, we go back
and take a look at the S3 bucket.
We'll have, if you're gonna go back to S3,
you'll see the aggregated folder here.
Go into that. You'll have the data within the
corresponding folders.
So can you tell me what the next step is?
What do you think should be the next step?
So we have load data for Jan 2094.
Obviously we have to load data for the two years,
2094 and 1 95.
But before that, what's the next step?
We gotta convert this notebook code to a script, right?
As you did in the previous, uh, part of the pipeline
where you load data from raw to curate it.
Right before that, you gotta stop the notebook,
otherwise you'll incur the cost.
You gotta just, um, first of all,
save this because it's all good.
Save the notebook and then
what you gonna do is you're gonna go to script.
Okay? Go to script and get the entire copy.
Go back to notebook and then finally stop.
So you copied the script, okay?
That script you'll use to create the glue, spark a TL job.
Just stop this for now. It is stop. Make sure you stop it.
And then the next step we'll create the glue,
spark et TL job.